{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which federal state has the largest area?",
        "options": ["Niedersachsen", "Bayern", "Baden-Württemberg", "Nordrhein-Westfalen"],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which city is the smallest in Germany in terms of both population and area?",
        "options": ["Neumark in Thüringen", "Schnackenburg in Niedersachsen", "Märkisch Buchholz in Brandenburg", "Arnis in Schleswig-Holstein"],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the largest island in Germany??",
        "options": ["Rügen", "Sylt", "Föhr", "Borkum"],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these rivers flows through Germany?",
        "options": ["Zusammen", "Zusa", "Zusam", "Zusamas"],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the largest entirely German lake?",
        "options": [
          "Müritz",
          "Chiemsee",
          "Bodensee",
          "Starnberger See"
        ],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "What was East Germany's capital?",
        "options": ["Hamburg", "Berlin", "Wuppertal", "Leipzig"],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Welche dieser Städte ist keine Hauptstadt eines Bundeslandes?",
        "options": [
          "Kiel",
          "Erfurt",
          "Dresden",
          "Bonn"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "Who unified Germany in 1871?",
        "options": [
          "Willy Brandt",
          "King Frederick William IV of Prussia",
          "Otto von Bismarck",
          "Boris Becker"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "Who did Prussia defeat in the 19th century to become the dominant German state?",
        "options": [
          "Saxony",
          "Bavaria",
          "Rhineland Palatinate",
          "Austria"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "Who did Goethe's Faust make a deal with?",
        "options": [
          "Mussolini",
          "The Bank of England",
          "Dracula",
          "The Devil"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "What did Karl Benz and Gottlieb Daimler invent?",
        "options": [
          "The doodlebug",
          "Lederhosen",
          "The motor car",
          "Five-hour operas"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was behind the printing press?",
        "options": ["Gebhard von Blücher", "Johannes Gutenberg", "Friedrich Schiller", "Martin Luther"],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "5. The Reinheitsgebot (purity law) relating to which product was laid down in 1516?",
        "options": [
          "Sauerkraut",
          "Sausage meat",
          "Beer",
          "Bread"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the number of federal states in Germany?",
        "options": [
          "16",
          "8",
          "18",
          "21"
        ],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of clock is Germany famous for producing?",
        "options": [
          "Grandfather",
          "Alarm",
          "Digital",
          "Cuckoo"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 20
      }
    ]
  }